gerson.org 2018-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Gerson Institute : Gerson Institute

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.gerson.org). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  * The security procedures in place to protect misuse of your information.
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

##### INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND SHARING

The Gerson Institute is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and will not sell or rent this information to anyone. The Gerson Institute’s access is limited to viewing and collecting information provided voluntarily via email or other direct contact.

The Gerson Institute will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us, and your information will not be shared with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

In the future, The Gerson Institute may contact you via email to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

You may opt-out of these email notifications by contacting us directly by email at [marketing@gerson.org](mailto:marketing@gerson.org), by telephone at 858-694-0707, or by logging in to your [online store account](https://checkout.na1.netsuite.com/c.3628325/checkout-2-03-0/index.ssp?ext=F&is=login&login=T&sc=1&_ga=2.217582870.1406912611.1507739239-1041541015.1500577143&reset=T#login-register) and accessing Settings >> Email Preferences.

##### YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION

You may opt-out of any future contact from us at any time by contacting us directly via email at [marketing@gerson.org](mailto:marketing@gerson.org), by telephone at 858-694-0707, or by logging in to your [online store account](https://checkout.na1.netsuite.com/c.3628325/checkout-2-03-0/index.ssp?ext=F&is=login&login=T&sc=1&_ga=2.217582870.1406912611.1507739239-1041541015.1500577143&reset=T#login-register) and accessing Settings >> Email Preferences.

You may also contact us at any time concerning the following:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

##### SECURITY

The Gerson Institute takes precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and offline.

Any sensitive information collected (such as credit card data) is encrypted and transimitted to us in a secure way. This can be verified by locating the closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or confirming that an “http” is at the beginning of the web page address.

While encryption is used to protect sensitive information transmitted online, your information is also protected offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computer/server in which personally identifiable information is stored is kept in a secure environment.

If you feel that the Gerson Institute is not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us immediately by email at [marketing@gerson.org](mailto:marketing@gerson.org) or by telephone at 858-694-0707.
